belboon.com 2013-06-23

# Privacy

We, belboon GmbH (Karl-Liebknecht-Straße 1, 10178 Berlin, Germany) take the protection of your personal data extremely seriously and adhere strictly to the regulations of the data protection acts. Personal data will only be collected on this website if it is technically required. The data collected will on no account be sold or given to third parties for other uses. The following explanation will provide you with an overview of how we guarantee this protection and which type of data is collected and for which purposes.

## Data collection on this internet site

As part of your belboon service, belboon GmbH automatically collects and saves data in your server log files, which your browser sends to us. These are:

  * Type/version of browser 
  * Operating system used 
  * Referrer URL (the site visited beforehand) 
  * Host name of the computer (IP address) 
  * Time of server request 

belboon GmbH can not match these data with specific persons. A combination of these data with other sources of data will not be carried out. Furthermore, the data will be deleted following statistical analysis.

## Cookies

So-called 'cookies' are used by websites in a number of areas. They help us to make our services more user-friendly, effective and safe. Cookies are small text files which are placed on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies used by us are so called "session cookies" and "tracking cookies". They are automatically deleted a few days after your visit. Cookies do not cause any damage to your computer and they do not contain viruses. Cookies from belboon GmbH can not be read by any third-party website.

The Usage of some of our services and offers is also possible without cookies. In your respective browser you can deactivate the storing of cookies under Tools/Internet Options, limit this to specific websites or set your browser such that it informs you as soon as a cookie is sent. You can also delete cookies from the hard drive of your PC at any time - e.g. Internet Explorer: Tools > Internet Options > Delete Browsing History / Cookies or in Firefox: Tools > Options > Privacy > Show Cookies > Remove Cookie / Remove All Cookies.   
The belboon domains are: belboon.com und belboon.de.   
Please note, however, that when so doing you must reckon with restricted presentation of the site and limited user guidance.

## Personal information and Emails

If you make use of the services that are offered on the www.belboon.de website, you agree to receive system messages, communications and newsletters via Email when you register. In order to do this, you need to provide us with a valid Email address as well as data that allow us to verify that you are the owner of the stated Email address or that its owner agrees to receive the newsletter. If you register with belboon you consent to the storage of your personal data, which you have provided to us via the respective forms for the purpose of the conclusion of the contract and for the use of belboon services. No further data will be collected in addition to this. At any given time, you can cancel the agreement regarding storage of your data, Email address as well as usage thereof for the sending of Emails and access provision. Data for the purposes of billing and accounting will remain unchanged in case of cancellation or deletion of your account.

## Right to Information

You have a right to information about the stored personal data, the origins of the data, further recipients as well as the purposes of data processing. The Data Protection Commissioner at belboon GmbH will be happy to inform you about the stored data (info@belboon.de).

## Further information

Your trust is important to us. We will be pleased to answer your questions regarding the processing of your personal data at any time. If you have any questions that have not been answered by this data protection declaration, or if you wish to receive more detailed information, please contact the Data Protection Commissioner at belboon GmbH (info@belboon.de) at any time. 

Berlin, 01.01.2009
